<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" media="screen" href="/~files/feed-premium.xsl"?>

<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:feedpress="https://feed.press/xmlns" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <feedpress:locale>en</feedpress:locale>
    <atom:link rel="self" href="http://feeds.dzone.com/home"/>
    <atom:link rel="hub" href="http://feedpress.superfeedr.com/"/>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://dzone.com</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Tips: jOOQ [Video]</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/spring-tips-jooq?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="10"&gt;Speaker: &lt;a href="https://www.twitter.com/starbuxman" rel="nofollow" style="background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);"&gt;Josh Long&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="9"&gt;Hi, Spring fans! In this tip, we’ll look at jOOQ (a fluent API for typesafe SQL query construction and execution) to quickly and easily interface with our SQL database.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>java</category>
      <category>tutorial</category>
      <category>spring</category>
      <category>jooq</category>
      <category>sql database</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 21:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1466751</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4347664&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Joshua Long</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Boot: A Quick Start</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/spring-boot-a-quick-start?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="2"&gt;In this article, we will create a simple Spring Boot application which will run on embedded Apache Tomcat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 pid="3"&gt;What Is Spring Boot?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p pid="4"&gt;Spring Boot helps in creating stand-alone, production-grade application easily with minimum fuss. It is the opinionated view of Spring framework and other third party libraries which believes in convenient configuration based setup.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>java</category>
      <category>tutorial</category>
      <category>spring boot</category>
      <category>web app development</category>
      <category>spring annotations</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 20:49:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1464855</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4351208&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Gaurav Rai Mazra</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Writing Comprehensive, Guaranteed, Up-to-Date REST API Documentation [Video]</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/writing-comprehensive-and-guaranteed-up-to-date-re?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="18"&gt;RESTful APIs are eating the world — yet all too often, the documentation can cause indigestion for the API developers and users. Developers have to deal with annotation overload, repetition, and an unpleasant writing environment. Users are then left with documentation that’s inaccurate and difficult to use. It doesn’t have to be this way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="15"&gt;This talk will introduce Spring REST docs and their test-driven approach to RESTful API documentation. We’ll look at how they combine&amp;nbsp;the power of Asciidoctor and your integration tests to produce documentation that’s accurate and easy-to-read while keeping your code DRY and free from annotation overload. We’ll also look at some of the features that are new in Spring REST Docs 1.1, including support for REST Assured and Markdown.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>integration</category>
      <category>documentation</category>
      <category>restful api</category>
      <category>spring rest docs</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 19:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1464895</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4348808&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Pieter Humphrey</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: ''High-Performance In-Memory Computing With Apache Ignite''</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-high-performance-in-memory-computing-with-apac?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="16" style="text-align: left;"&gt;My first acquaintance with high load systems was at the beginning of 2007. I started working on a real-world project in 2009. From that moment on, I've spent most of my office time with Cassandra, Hadoop, and numerous CEP tools. Our first Hadoop project (in 2011-2012) with a cluster of 54 nodes often disappoints me with its long startup time. I have never been satisfied with the performance of our applications and I'm always looking for something new to boost the performance of our information systems. During this time, I have tried HazelCast, Ehcache, and Oracle Coherence as in-memory caches to gain the performance of applications. I was usually disappointed in the complexity of using this library for functional limitations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: left;" pid="18"&gt;When I first encountered Apache Ignite, I was amazed. It was the platform that I'd been waiting on for a long time: a simple Spring-based framework with a lot of awesome features such as database caching, big data acceleration, streaming, and compute/service grids.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>big data</category>
      <category>application performance</category>
      <category>apache ignite</category>
      <category>in-memory computing</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 19:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1458527</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4351071&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Shamim Bhuiyan</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magento 2 vs Magento 1: Do You Need Upgrade?</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/magento-2-vs-magento-1-do-you-need-upgrade?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="2"&gt;We remember the time when we were waiting for Magento 2 release and were so excited when it happened. The Magento team put a lot of effort into that release and delighted us with new improvements. Since that time, many store owners have become curious to know if they should move the store from Magento 1 to Magento 2 and if so – when it should happen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="3"&gt;So, we’ve done some research on what has been added or changed in Magento 2 in comparison with Magento 1 to collect more information for our clients when they ask us the question: “to be or not to be” with Magento 2. In this article, you will find the main&lt;a href="http://www.pixelcrayons.com/blog/cms/woocommerce-vs-magento-vs-opencart/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt; changes and an improvements overview.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>web dev</category>
      <category>magento development</category>
      <category>retail management</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 18:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1465690</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4351406&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>MARIA ZAYAC</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scrum is Not Agile</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/scrum-is-not-agile-part-1-of-2-jade-stephen?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="2"&gt;Last week I was speaking with another Agile practitioner about forming some new teams. During our discussion, I was told that Kanban would be the only way to proceed, because “Scrum is not Agile.” This stance seems to be growing in popularity. I frequently see posters on LinkedIn sharing that they signed the “agile oath of non-allegiance” or talking about Scrum as if it were a rigid process that must be followed to the letter. As a Scrum Master, I instinctively dislike this opinion. In an attempt to challenge my assumptions, I want to see if this could be true. Is Scrum an agile framework?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="3"&gt;To truly answer that question, I need to establish what Agile is. The inciting incident shows that there must be competing opinions. &amp;nbsp;For the sake of this inspection, I will use the most incorruptible definition I can think of, the &lt;em&gt;Agile Manifesto&lt;/em&gt;. In this post, I will compare Scrum to the first two of four key principles. Next week, I will finish out my investigation with the remaining two.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>agile</category>
      <category>scrum</category>
      <category>development process</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 18:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1461443</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4351454&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Jade Stephen</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Week in Spring: Distributed Tracing, Microservices, and REST</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/this-week-in-spring-february-14th-2017?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="4"&gt;Welcome to another installment of &lt;em&gt;This Week in Spring!&lt;/em&gt; It was Valentine's Day for some, and so happy Valentine's Day to you! This week, I’m in Memphis, Tennessee, for business, then it’s off to St. Louis, where I’ll be presenting on &lt;a href="https://www.meetup.com/Saint-Louis-Spring-Meetup/events/236875279/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank" style="background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);"&gt;Reactive Spring with my buddy Mark Heckler (join us!)&lt;/a&gt;, then it’s off to Atlanta, Georgia, ahead of next week’s &lt;a href="https://www.devnexus.com/s/speakers/1284" rel="nofollow" target="_blank" style="background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);"&gt;big DevNexus show&lt;/a&gt;. Check out &lt;a href="https://spring.io/blog/2017/02/01/spring-team-at-devnexus-2017" rel="nofollow" target="_blank" style="background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);"&gt;what Pivotal is up to at the event!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="3"&gt;As usual, we’ve got a lot to cover so let’s get going!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>java</category>
      <category>microservices</category>
      <category>spring cloud</category>
      <category>distributed tracing</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 17:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1466756</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4347723&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Joshua Long</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From the Neo4j Community: January 2017</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/from-the-neo4j-community-january-2017?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="7"&gt;The year is off to a great start when to comes to the Neo4j community. If this month is any indication of what’s to come, then we know that 2017 will be a big year for Neo4j projects, drivers and integrations across the board. Here are some of our favorite picks from last month’s Neo4j community contributions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="2"&gt;If you would like to see&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;your&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;post featured in February’s “From the Neo4j Community” blog post,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://twitter.com/Neo4j" target="_blank"&gt;follow us on Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://twitter.com/hashtag/neo4j" target="_blank"&gt;use the #Neo4j hashtag&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for your chance to get picked.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>database</category>
      <category>neo4j</category>
      <category>graph database</category>
      <category>graph visualization</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 17:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1465768</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4346075&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Mark Needham</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scrum Myths: Scrum Projects are Faster and Cheaper</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/scrum-myths-scrum-projects-are-faster-and-cheaper?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="24"&gt;The myth I am debunking in this post is that Scrum projects are faster and cheaper. This myth is my favorite. There are three challenges with this presumption.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;First, it misses the point of Scrum.&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;Second, it sets teams up for failure.&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;Third, it’s impossible to prove.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p pid="3"&gt;I assert that there is a &lt;em&gt;bit&lt;/em&gt; of truth in this myth. However, it’s not as simple as saying Project X will be cheaper and faster if we use Scrum to deliver it. Let me explain.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>agile</category>
      <category>scrum</category>
      <category>development process</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 17:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1464830</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4334787&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>stephanieockerman</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should I Test at the GUI Level or the API Level?</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/should-i-test-at-the-gui-level-or-the-api-level?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="35"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Question:&lt;/strong&gt; Is there a rule of thumb when deciding to test at the GUI level or API level? Are any rules to help decide when to test at one level over the other?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="8"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Answer: &lt;/strong&gt;I don’t think I use a simple rule of thumb — but I will try and explore some of the thought processes I use to make the decision.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>gui</category>
      <category>devops</category>
      <category>api</category>
      <category>software testing</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 17:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1466745</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4346026&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Alan Richardson</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpringOne Replay: Real World Microservices With Spring Cloud, Netflix OSS, and Kubernetes [Video]</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/springone-replay-real-world-microservices-with-spring-cloud-netflix-oss-and-kubernetes?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="1"&gt;Building distributed systems — whether we call them SOA or microservices - is not easy. Open source communities like Spring, Netflix OSS, and Kubernetes bring decades of experience building these systems, but the question always begs to be asked, “Do we implement these patterns in the application layer or in the infrastructure layer?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="3"&gt;This is a Java developer-oriented presentation showing developers how to approach building microservices in the real world (influenced by experiences at large enterprise customers) using application-level components like Spring, Spring Cloud, and Netflix OSS and running them on infrastructure components like Docker and Kubernetes. We’ll cover some gotchas, patterns, and overall best practices for developing with this ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>cloud</category>
      <category>microservices</category>
      <category>kubernetes</category>
      <category>spring cloud</category>
      <category>netflix oss</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 17:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1466733</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4345792&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Pieter Humphrey</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 Mobile Commerce Trends in 2017 [Infographic]</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/6-mobile-commerce-trends-in-2017-infographic?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="2"&gt;We are living in a mobile era, and mobility advantages have won minds and hearts of the people of all strata. Rapidly developing mobile technologies have set mobile commerce trends in the recent past and it is likely continuing in the coming year 2017.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="53" style="text-align: center;"&gt;&lt;em&gt;This infographic brought to you by &lt;a href="http://www.perceptionsystem.com/mobile-device-application-development.html" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;Perception System&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>mobile</category>
      <category>ecommerce</category>
      <category>augmented reality</category>
      <category>mobile commerce</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 17:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1466505</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4350016&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Moses Aaron</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming IoT Events in March 2017</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/upcoming-iot-events-in-march-2017?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="1"&gt;It’s no surprise that there are many, MANY, Internet of Things (IoT) events happening all over the world every month. But, there are a few taking place next month that I am particularly excited about. Whether you live in North America, France, or Germany there is an IoT event for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="2"&gt;Now, get ready to mark your calendars!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>iot</category>
      <category>iot development</category>
      <category>iot security</category>
      <category>edge computing</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 17:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1465143</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4349853&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Roxanne Joncas</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Middleware Fits Into the API Lifecycle</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/api-lifemiddlewarecycle-api?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="2"&gt;I have had a series of calls with an analyst group lately discussing the overall API landscape in 2017. They have a lot of interesting questions about the space, and I enjoyed their level of curiosity and awareness around what is going on — it helps me think through this stuff and (hopefully) better explain it to folks who aren't immersed in APIs like I am.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="3"&gt;This particular group is coming at it from a middleware perspective and is trying to understand what APIs have done to the middleware market and what opportunities exist (if any). This starting point for an API conversation got me thinking about the concept of middleware in contrast (or relation) to what I'm seeing emerge as the services and tooling for the API life cycle.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>integration</category>
      <category>api</category>
      <category>middleware</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 15:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1464902</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4348750&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Kin Lane</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Ship Kibana Server Logs to Elasticsearch</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-ship-kibana-server-logs-to-elasticsearch-1?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="26"&gt;When dealing with log centralization in your organization, you have to start with something. Often times, people start by collecting logs for the most crucial pieces of software. Frequently, one chooses to ship them to their own in-house Elasticsearch-based solution (ELK stack) or one of the SaaS solutions available on the market. What we regularly see in our &lt;a href="https://sematext.com/consulting/logging/" target="_blank" style="background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);"&gt;logging consulting practice&lt;/a&gt; and with our Logsene users is that it’s just a matter of time before everyone in the organization realizes how useful it is to have centralized logs and starts sending logs from every crucial software/IT — and business — component in the organization to the log centralization system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="3"&gt;Despite Kibana being frequently used for log analysis and reporting, Kibana is one of those pieces whose own logs are often left behind. Kibana is no longer a simple set of static JavaScript files...not since version 4. It is a Node.js application and as such it produces its own logs, too. They can provide insight when something is not right with Kibana, so why put them in the same place as all the other logs? Let’s see how to do that.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>tutorial</category>
      <category>big data</category>
      <category>kibana</category>
      <category>logs</category>
      <category>elk</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 15:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1464546</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4360728&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Rafal Kuc</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementing Feature Flags in Single-Page Apps With React and Redux Saga</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/implementing-feature-flags-in-single-page-apps-usi?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="73"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Built on frameworks like &lt;a href="https://facebook.github.io/react/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;React&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://angularjs.org/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;Angular&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="http://emberjs.com/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;Ember&lt;/a&gt;, single-page apps (SPA) are becoming the new norm for modern applications. They center around dynamically updating a single HTML page via AJAX and HTML5 to deliver a more fluid and faster user experience. This introduces some new complexity when it comes to controlling access to front-end features, specifically via feature flags.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="73"&gt;Feature flags (toggles) are used to gate access to particular code snippets, allowing you to control a feature’s rollout, target specific users, and kill a feature in production. The challenge with feature flagging single-page apps is handling the state transformations &lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;(the changes in a webpage’s DOM)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;in a way that maintains performance and a fluid user experience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>devops</category>
      <category>react</category>
      <category>regex</category>
      <category>feature flags</category>
      <category>single page apps</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 15:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1464889</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4350923&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Justin Baker</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Data Storage Solutions for Better Log Management</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/5-data-storages-for-better-log-management?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="6"&gt;Servers generate a large number of events (logs) that contain important information including operation errors, warnings, and users' behavior. By default, most servers store these data in plain text log files on their local file systems. While plain-text logs are accessible and human-readable, they are difficult to use, reference and analyze without holistic systems for aggregating and storing data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr" pid="4"&gt;The solution for storing big data is a huge technical challenge nowadays. Of course, there are different options such as RDBMS, NoSQL, time-series databases, etc. LogPacker gives users the&amp;nbsp;freedom to choose among 15 supported data providers. In this article, we analyze five storage solutions for saving large amounts (a few TB of data) of logs generated on multiple instances.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>performance</category>
      <category>log management</category>
      <category>data storage</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 15:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1463103</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4360843&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Vladislav Chernov</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Developer’s Stages of Grief After a Failed Security Assessment: Part One</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/a-developers-stages-of-grief-after-a-failed-securi?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="34"&gt;After nearly 10 years as a security consultant, I've talked to thousands of developers about &lt;a href="http://www.veracode.com/services/developer-coaching" title="Veracode Developer Coaching" style="background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);"&gt;remediating security flaws&lt;/a&gt; in their code. It's not always an easy conversation, and developers have a wide range of emotional reactions, not all of them good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="5"&gt;The fact is, developers are increasingly responsible for quality assurance and security testing of their code, tasks that didn’t used to be part of their job descriptions. Software development is undergoing a massive shift with the rise of &lt;a href="http://www.veracode.com/blog/secure-development/future-appsec-devsecops" title="The Future of AppSec Is DevSecOps"&gt;DevOps&lt;/a&gt;, and it means big changes for developers.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>security</category>
      <category>devops</category>
      <category>testing</category>
      <category>collaboration</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 13:31:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1464507</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4320764&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Jim Jastrzebski</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Predict Productivity in Agile Teams With Statistics</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-predict-productivity-in-agile-teams-with-st?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="2"&gt;What do you say when your clients ask: 'So, when will the project be done?'&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="3"&gt;If your team ends up living in the office to meet the deadline you are doing it wrong. Instead of trying to determine the future, use data analysis and statistics to give a probabilistic prediction, based on historical data collected from your own process.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>agile</category>
      <category>kanban</category>
      <category>predictive analytics</category>
      <category>productivity tools</category>
      <category>statistical analysis</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 13:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1465729</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4329675&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Dmytro Moroz</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrating a Legacy Application to CUBA Platform</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/migrating-a-legacy-application-to-cuba-platform?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="1" style="text-align: left;"&gt;Sometimes it appears that the underlying stack of technologies used for an application is no longer appropriate for further software development and support. It may happen for a big variety of reasons: used technology is old and not supported anymore; legacy application doesn't meet new technical or customer requirements, that are hardly implementable using the old stack; or, finally, you have to support an application developed by a third-party company, but don't have enough experience and confidence in the used technology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="2"&gt;So, what if you got to the point when your legacy application should be migrated? We decided to provide a step by step guide and show how to modernize a legacy application with minimum efforts, taking the LightSwitch platform as an example, which has &lt;a href="https://blogs.msdn.microsoft.com/lightswitch/2016/10/14/lightswitch-update/" target="_blank"&gt;officially been abandoned by Microsoft&lt;/a&gt;. CUBA Studio comes along with its migration tool, which streamlines the migration process and makes it very straightforward and transparent. To demonstrate how it works in practice we moved the &lt;a href="https://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/ee256749.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;Vision Clinic LightSwitch sample application&lt;/a&gt; to CUBA Platform and &lt;a href="https://github.com/cuba-platform/cuba-vision-clinic/" target="_blank"&gt;described all steps on the official platform GitHub&lt;/a&gt;. Below you can see the old LightSwitch and new CUBA screenshots of the same screen, used in the Vision Clinic application.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>java</category>
      <category>tutorial</category>
      <category>migration</category>
      <category>legacy app</category>
      <category>cuba platform</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 11:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1457964</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4360671&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Aleksey Stukalov</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dev Security: Authentication Is More Important Than Ever in 2017</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/authentication-is-more-important-than-ever-in-2017?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="3"&gt;In this digital world, hackers reign supreme. Sad fact but true nonetheless. New technologies and companies being too frugal with their security budgets has concocted the perfect storm for more sophisticated threat mechanisms. In turn, this made cyber security a necessity =. Governments and companies have finally acknowledged its importance and started pouring big bucks into data protection. The increased funding has led to better and more efficient authentication trends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="4"&gt;According to Gartner, “user authentication” is the real time corroboration of a person’s claimed digital identity with an implied or notional level of trust. The three main authentication methods are single factor authentication (password mediated), &lt;a href="https://www.vasco.com/two-factor-authentication.html" rel="dofollow"&gt;two-factor authentication&lt;/a&gt;, and multi-factor authentication.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>security</category>
      <category>authenciation</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 10:31:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1462737</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4301432&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Annie Qureshi</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Deep Dive Into Telerik UI for NativeScript's SideDrawer</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/a-deep-dive-into-telerik-ui-for-nativescripts-side?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="2"&gt;When planning your mobile app, how soon in the process are you considering your user interface? Do you have the plans and designs in place to build not only a robust app, but one which delights and engages your customers?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="3"&gt;For nearly 15 years now, the &lt;a href="http://www.telerik.com/devcraft" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;Telerik UI components&lt;/a&gt; have been in millions of developer's hands. From .NET to JavaScript, Xamarin to PHP, Telerik UI components have allowed you to build engaging apps and have helped make you a more productive developer.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>mobile</category>
      <category>tutorial</category>
      <category>ui</category>
      <category>nativescript</category>
      <category>sidedrawer</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 10:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1466786</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4360793&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Rob Lauer</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adopta.Agency in the Trump Administration</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/adoptaagency-in-the-trump-administration?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="2"&gt;&lt;a href="http://adopta.agency" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;Adopta.Agency&lt;/a&gt; is an ongoing project for me. I'm still using the template as a&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://adopta-agency.github.io/adopta-blueprint/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank" style="background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);"&gt;basis for some custom open data work&lt;/a&gt;, but I wanted to pause for a moment and think about what Adopta.Agency means to me in a Trump administration. The need for&amp;nbsp;Adopta.Agency is greater than ever. We need an army of civic-minded individuals to step in and help be stewards of public data. The current administration does not see value in making government more transparent, something that will trickle down to all levels of government, making what we do much more difficult.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="3"&gt;To be honest, after the election, I hit a pretty big low regarding what I should be doing with open data at the federal level. Now, in February, I feel little more optimistic. I want to set a handful of Adopta.Agency goals for myself and think more about the project in the Trump Administration. In the next couple of months I want to:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>big data</category>
      <category>government</category>
      <category>public data</category>
      <category>adopta.agency</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 10:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1466777</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4350845&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Kin Lane</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Export All Plans From Cache to a .SQLPLAN File [Snippet]</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/export-all-plans-from-cache-to-a-sqlplan-file?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="1"&gt;I was asked if there was an easy way to export all the plans from cache to a .SQLPLAN file. My immediate answer was, “I’m sure there’s a PowerShell script out there somewhere.” However, rather than do a Google search, I figured I’d quickly knock up an example.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="2"&gt;I’ve gone minimal on the script. I’m creating a connection to the local instance, defining a command, and returning the data into a data set. From there, since the data set consists of a single column, I’m walking through them all to export out to a file:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>database</category>
      <category>sql server</category>
      <category>powershell</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 10:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1466752</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4360692&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Grant Fritchey</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employee Attendance App: A Great Way to Make Your Team’s Life a Whole Lot Easier</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/employee-attendance-app-a-great-way-to-make-your-t?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="2"&gt;Attendance management systems have been around for a long time and can vary wildly from the most rudimentary stuff like punch cards and sign-in logs to more advanced and costly solutions based on RFID technology or biometrics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="4"&gt;And when it comes to tracking employee attendance, some modern companies tend to brush these systems off (often rightfully so) as either too expensive or overly intrusive and controlling, choosing instead to rely on their management personnel to keep their teams under control. Others don’t see any value in tracking attendance at all, trusting their employees to be actually present at work when they’re supposed to.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>agile</category>
      <category>time management</category>
      <category>human resources</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 10:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1465684</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4327866&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Arina Katrycheva</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Evolution of a Linux Container</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-evolution-of-a-linux-container?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="67"&gt;Probably, a more accurate title would be “The Evolution of a Linux Container Developer.” Since .NET now runs on Linux (as well as Windows and macOS), the whole world of Linux containers and microservices has opened up to .NET developers. With a large pool of developers, a long track record of success, and performance numbers that are impressive, .NET offers a great opportunity to expand the world of Linux containers to formerly Windows-centric developers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="69"&gt;While it’s tempting to rush in — and I am the first to say, “go for it” — there are some nuances which should not be missed when running .NET code inside a Linux container. It’s far too easy to push some code into an image and be done. After all, everything happens so quickly, surely all is well. Right?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>.net</category>
      <category>cloud</category>
      <category>tutorial</category>
      <category>docker</category>
      <category>linux containers</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 10:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1465233</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4360683&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Don Schenck</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Types of Anypoint Filters With Mulesoft</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/different-types-of-anypoint-filters-in-mulesoft?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="1"&gt;&lt;a href="https://docs.mulesoft.com/mule-user-guide/v/3.8/filters" rel="nofollow" target="_blank" style="background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255); font-family: Georgia, serif; font-size: 19px; font-weight: normal;"&gt;Filters&lt;/a&gt; in Mule flows play a vital role in deciding whether messages can be passed to other message processors or not. When a&amp;nbsp;message reaches a filter in the flow and meets the required conditions, then it passed to other processors in the&amp;nbsp;flow. Otherwise, flow execution will be terminated and no more processing will be done.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 pid="8"&gt;Idempotent Filter&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p pid="13"&gt;The&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://docs.mulesoft.com/mule-user-guide/v/3.8/idempotent-filter" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;idempotent filter&lt;/a&gt; is one of the most&amp;nbsp;important filters when it comes to processing unique messages within a flow. You can set &lt;code&gt;Id Expression&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;using MEL to identify the duplicate message on basis of the expression defined. The default expression used is &lt;code&gt;#[message:id]&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>integration</category>
      <category>mulesoft</category>
      <category>filters</category>
      <category>anypoint</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 10:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1465059</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4348696&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Jitendra Bafna</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How We Improved Our Server Performance</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-we-improved-our-server-performance-to-100m-mes?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="44"&gt;One of the key features of Thingsboard's open-source IoT platform is data collection. This is a&amp;nbsp;crucial feature that must work reliably under high loads. In this article, we are going to describe steps and improvements that can help ensure that a single instance of the&amp;nbsp;Thingsboard server can constantly handle 20,000+ devices and 30,000+ MQTT publish messages per second — which gives us around two million published messages per minute.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="architecture"&gt;Architecture&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p pid="3"&gt;Thingsboard performance leverages three main projects:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>performance</category>
      <category>scaling</category>
      <category>iot platform</category>
      <category>performance tests</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 10:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1464828</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4346017&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Andrew Shvayka</dc:creator>
      <dc:creator>Volodymyr Babak</dc:creator>
      <dc:creator>Igor Kulikov</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python vs PHP vs Ruby: A Detailed Comparison</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/python-vs-php-vs-ruby-detailed-comparison?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p open="" pid="2"&gt;Which programming language should you learn? &lt;a href="http://www.pixelcrayons.com/blog/web/php-vs-python-vs-ruby-comparison/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;Python, PHP or Ruby&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p open="" pid="3"&gt;Possibly the biggest question facing web development newbies is which language is best to learn for their future career and prospects. There are many programming languages to choose from and each has its own strengths and weaknesses. Possibly the most important concern is how long each language takes to learn and this varies for each language. So which should you learn for the best chance at a successful career in programming? Besides Python and Ruby, one of the biggest competitors of PHP is ASP.NET, in my previous article &lt;a href="http://www.pixelcrayons.com/blog/web/php-vs-asp-net-how-to-choose-the-right-one/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;PHP vs ASP.NET&lt;/a&gt;, I have given a detailed comparison of these two main languages.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>php</category>
      <category>ruby</category>
      <category>python</category>
      <category>web dev</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 10:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1465575</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4350975&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Prateek Tiwari</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ensuring Continuous Delivery With Test Automation</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ensure-continuous-delivery-in-agile-testing-cycles?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="2"&gt;Quality at speed is what every enterprise strives for these days. With increasing business demands to accelerate time-to-market, more and more companies have started migrating from traditional development methods to Continuous Delivery that are based on Agile philosophy. This modern approach allows software to be developed and deployed in short cycles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="3"&gt;Companies are rapidly embracing Agile practices to accelerate the application delivery to cope with the strict demands of the market. The modern landscape of software testing not only focuses on speedy delivery but also necessitates quality. It becomes imperative for the companies to follow a continuous schedule that encourages frequent releases without affecting the quality.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>devops</category>
      <category>continuous delivery</category>
      <category>test automation</category>
      <category>agile testing</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 10:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1446947</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4335974&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>William Kimmel</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Random Generator to Maven Central</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/introducing-random-generator-to-maven-central?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="2"&gt;Continuing with my series on a library I have created, called RandomGenerator, I am going to focus on the steps necessary to getting the library into Maven Central so that others can utilize my creation in their Java projects. I will also include a simple example of using RandomGenerator in a Maven project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="5"&gt;If you need to get up to speed on RandomGenerator, below are links to my prior articles in this series:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>java</category>
      <category>tutorial</category>
      <category>randomness</category>
      <category>maven central</category>
      <category>generator</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 08:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1464024</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4310783&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>John Vester</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Look Into Log Analysis and Effective Critical Alerting</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/a-look-into-log-analysis-and-effective-critical-al?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="2"&gt;The Great Wall of China began construction in 7 B.C. to protect the Chinese kingdom from Eurasian warriors. Chinese soldiers would marshal forces to protect the Great Wall from enemy attack by using smoke signals to send alerts from tower to tower. This method of alerting enabled messages to be sent to garrisons hundreds of miles away in just a few hours time. With these alerts, soldiers could prepare to convene and combat their enemies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="3"&gt;How can teams effectively analyze this vast amount of data from their various systems? How can they use this data to troubleshoot issues when they do arrive? How can they use this data to prepare for the IT dangers they know of and those that are unforeseen? Furthermore, how can they make sure they are alerted when serious issues and even dangers arrive?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>devops</category>
      <category>log analysis</category>
      <category>elk</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 06:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1466775</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4350802&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Orlee Berlove</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Random Calls Home that an Application Makes from My Home</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-random-calls-home-that-an-application-makes-fr?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="2"&gt;I have been running &lt;a href="https://www.charlesproxy.com/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank" style="background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);"&gt;Charles Proxy&lt;/a&gt; locally for quite some time now. &lt;a href="http://apievangelist.com/2016/02/05/automated-mapping-of-the-api-universe-with-charles-proxy-dropbox-openapi-spec-and-some-custom-apis/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank" style="background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);"&gt;I began using it to reverse engineer the APIs behind some mobile applications&lt;/a&gt; and continued to use it to map out the APIs I'm depending on each day. I regularly turn on Charles Proxy and export the listing of any HTTP calls made while I'm working, every five minutes. These files get moved up into the cloud using Dropbox, where I have a regular CRON job processing each call made — profiling the domain, and details of the request and response for later review.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="3"&gt;This process has shed some light on the application architecture of many of the tools and services I depend on. It's fascinating to see the number of pings home the average application will make when on, or running in the background. In addition to running Charles Proxy and understanding how these applications are communicating with their mothership, from within my home, I downloaded &lt;a href="https://www.zdziarski.com/blog/?page_id=6171" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;Little Flocker&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;— providing me a peek at another layer of application architecture, and how they interact with my laptop.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>iot</category>
      <category>iot apps</category>
      <category>integrations</category>
      <category>iot analytics</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 06:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1464896</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4360762&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Kin Lane</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Practices for Tracing and Debugging Microservices</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/best-practices-for-tracing-and-debugging-microserv?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="2"&gt;In this article, I’ll be talking about some techniques for debugging and fault-finding in microservices architectures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="5"&gt;One of the issues we’ve had for a long time — in fact, ever since distributed computing became a thing — has to do with debugging issues with a single business process that is run across multiple machines at different times. When software was monolithic, we always had access to the full execution stack trace and we knew the machine that we were running on. When we encountered an error, we could write all the information we needed to a log and later inspect it to see what went wrong.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>performance</category>
      <category>microservices</category>
      <category>logging</category>
      <category>debugging</category>
      <category>tracing</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 06:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1464893</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4345803&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Andrew Rivers</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intro to Python CSV Processing for Actual Beginners</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/intro-to-python-csv-processing-for-actual-beginner?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="3"&gt;I've written quite a bit about &lt;a href="http://slott-softwarearchitect.blogspot.com/search/label/csv." rel="nofollow" target="_blank" style="background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);"&gt;CSV processing&lt;/a&gt;. It crops up in my books. A lot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="9"&gt;In all cases, though, I make the implicit assumption that my readers already know a lot of Python. This is a disservice to anyone who's getting started.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>python</category>
      <category>web dev</category>
      <category>csv</category>
      <category>jupyter notebook</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 06:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1464827</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4360990&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Steven Lott</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Secret to a Superior Product Owner</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-secret-to-a-superior-product-owner?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="2"&gt;The world of Agile has been a welcomed change for those who lived through the Waterfall development days. Gone are the weeks, if not months, of business analysts drafting volumes of static requirements that only reflected an invalid state when the development team finally got around to working on the project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="5"&gt;When the Agile framework reached the common workplace, the business analyst was replaced with product owners and product managers. Their timelines were compressed into smaller, easier to digest, segments of work - providing solutions to the requester on a more routine cadence.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>agile</category>
      <category>waterfall</category>
      <category>product owner</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 06:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1464559</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4324147&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>John Vester</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hadoop 101: HBase and Client Access</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/hadoop-101-hbase-client-access?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="1"&gt;In the current stable version of &lt;a href="https://hadoop.apache.org" rel="nofollow" target="_blank" style="background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);"&gt;Hadoop 2.7.3&lt;/a&gt;, there are a lot of projects, features, and parts. I will walk you through using the most important and widely used tools, as well as provide tips and techniques for maximizing your usage of your Hadoop Data Lake.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="3"&gt;The first piece we'll look at is&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://hbase.apache.org/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;HBase&lt;/a&gt;. Apache HBase is a pretty awesome NoSQL store on top of Zookeeper and storing data in HDFS. It's based on the legendary Google BigTable and is known for scaling to massive size and supporting fast reads.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>nosql</category>
      <category>big data</category>
      <category>hadoop</category>
      <category>hbase</category>
      <category>data lakes</category>
      <category>client access</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 06:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1463695</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4348905&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Tim Spann</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrating to Microservices</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/migrating-to-microservices?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="2"&gt;This article details the steps to migrate an existing monolithic application to microservices, an architectural approach that consists of building systems from small services, each in their own process, communicating over lightweight protocols. This will provide a broad view of microservices implementation in Azure using service fabric, challenges faced in migration, approaches, and strategies that we can implement, and ways to build, release, monitor, and scale microservices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="4"&gt;This article deals with an innovative practice that has the potential to be used across different projects.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>tutorial</category>
      <category>architecture</category>
      <category>microservices</category>
      <category>migration</category>
      <category>azure service fabric</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 06:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1451350</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4335931&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Abhijit Mandal</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controlling VGA Memory with x86 Assembly Code</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/controlling-vga-memory-with-x86-assembly-code?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p dir="ltr" pid="301"&gt;This article is intended to make you familiar with controlling VGA with x86 assembly. Yes, we don’t hear much in the field of Assembly Language programming, as it is not quite as popular as compared to other programming and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://www.cleverism.com/programming-languages-web-development/" rel="nofollow"&gt;web development languages&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;such as &lt;a href="https://simple.wikipedia.org/wiki/Java_(programming_language)" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.w3schools.com/tags/ref_language_codes.asp" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;HTML&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://getbootstrap.com/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;Bootstrap,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;or&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://mbg.com.sg/digital-marketing/search-engine-marketing-sem/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;SEM&lt;/a&gt;. But it is essential on its own and knowledge of it proves to be quite helpful in understanding how computers work internally. Of course, you need to be familiar with x86 assembly beforehand which includes knowing the instruction set as well as concepts of registers, operations, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="350"&gt;The setup that you will need includes installing ‘dosbox’ as well as ‘EMU8086’ on your machine. Install both of them. EMU8086 is intended to compile our source code into machine code, and then we will run the compiled code inside the environment that Dosbox will provide. After you’ve installed them, open up EMU8086, create a new&lt;em&gt; ‘.COM’&lt;/em&gt; file, and then paste the following code inside the editor:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>web dev</category>
      <category>assembly</category>
      <category>x86</category>
      <category>vga memory</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 06:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1465501</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4349350&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Nadir Yaqoob</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is RASP Scalable?</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/is-rasp-scalable?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="2"&gt;The short answer is: Yes. RASP is scalable when it is implemented correctly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What is RASP?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p pid="3"&gt;Runtime application self-protection (RASP) is not a single technology. It is a concept — that protecting the application from within is the most efficient and effective way to provide true security for web applications. Different vendors interpret it in different ways and with sometimes vastly different approaches.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>security</category>
      <category>scalability</category>
      <category>rasp</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 05:31:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1443626</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4332981&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Mike Milner</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating a Self-Routing Varnish Cluster</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/creating-a-self-routing-varnish-cluster?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="29"&gt;In this article, I will explain how to create a highly available, self-routing sharded &lt;a href="https://www.varnish-software.com/varnish-cache/" target="_blank" style="background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);"&gt;Varnish Cache&lt;/a&gt; cluster. This is similar to a standard sharded cluster with one exception, there is no dedicated routing tier. Each node in the cluster can route the request to the proper destination node, by itself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="2"&gt;From an architecture standpoint, having a self-routing cluster is an interesting proposition because it means no load balancer or application router is needed. All we need is DNS. Routing logic, which before had a dedicated piece of hardware or software, is now distributed across all participating nodes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>cloud</category>
      <category>tutorial</category>
      <category>routing</category>
      <category>varnish</category>
      <category>clustered computing</category>
      <category>self-routing architecture</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 05:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1465766</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4345638&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Reza Naghibi</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effective Self-Service Analytics Depends on Database Preparation</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/effective-self-service-analytics-depends-on-database-preparation?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="2"&gt;The promise of self-service business intelligence (BI) is that it allows application end users to create their own reports, dashboards, and data visualizations by running queries on the fly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="4"&gt;However, if organizations undertaking a project to deliver self-service analytics do not consider the infrastructure that will support the new solution, even the best BI and analytics project will fail to meet end user expectations. This failure can often be attributed to a lack of database preparation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>database</category>
      <category>business intelligence</category>
      <category>database application development</category>
      <category>self-service analytics</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 05:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1464865</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4360954&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Roseanne Winn</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why You Should Focus on iOS Localization</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/why-you-should-focus-on-ios-localization?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="2"&gt;If you’ve made a resolution list for your business this year, localization should be on it. More specifically,&amp;nbsp;mobile app localization. Why? Because the app market is experiencing explosive growth. The number of mobile subscribers globally is close to&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://www.statista.com/statistics/274774/forecast-of-mobile-phone-users-worldwide/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank" style="background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);"&gt;4.77 billion in 2017&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;— and they’re becoming more demanding. With millions of apps available, users won’t bother downloading your English app if there’s a local version available. Android localization or iOS localization have become essential.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="8"&gt;Faced with so many different choices, mobile users are no longer held hostage to the few apps that came with their operating system. They don’t need to book a regular flight, stay in a standard hotel, or call a taxi to take them to the airport. There’s an app that pretty much covers everything and customizes the experience for them.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>mobile</category>
      <category>ios</category>
      <category>i18n</category>
      <category>l10n</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 05:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1460513</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4350062&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>David Ost</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Git Forks And Upstreams: How-to and a Cool Tip</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/git-forks-and-upstreams-how-to-and-a-cool-tip?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="2"&gt;There are tons and then some useful guides on how to keep your &lt;a href="https://www.atlassian.com/git/tutorials/comparing-workflows/forking-workflow"&gt;&lt;code&gt;forks&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt; updated against the &lt;code&gt;upstream&lt;/code&gt; repositories (and if you're wondering why you would want to use forks in an enterprise setting, check out a few reasons here). In this blog, I will introduce you to few aspects of how forking interacts with &lt;code&gt;upstream&lt;/code&gt;: the basics, the gotcha's, and an cool tip. To top it off I will then make you very jealous, or very eager, the choice is yours. Interested? Read on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The Base Workflow to Keep Up-to-Date and Contribute&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p pid="3"&gt;Let me start by detailing a common setup and the most basic workflow to interact with &lt;code&gt;upstream&lt;/code&gt; repositories.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>java</category>
      <category>tutorial</category>
      <category>git</category>
      <category>forking</category>
      <category>upstream</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 05:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1460314</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4349958&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Nicola Paolucci</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Execute Spark Code on Spark Shell With Cassandra</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/spark-cassandra-connector-on-spark-shell?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="21"&gt;In this blog, we will see how to execute our Spark code on Spark shell using Cassandra. This is very efficient when it comes to testing and learning and when we have to execute our code on a Spark shell rather than doing so on an IDE.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="3"&gt;Here, we will use Spark v1.6.2.You can download the version from &lt;a href="http://spark.apache.org/downloads.html" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; and its appropriate spark Cassandra connector,&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;spark-cassandra-connector_2.10-1.6.2.jar&lt;/code&gt;, can be downloaded from &lt;a href="https://mvnrepository.com/artifact/com.datastax.spark/spark-cassandra-connector_2.10/1.6.2" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>tutorial</category>
      <category>big data</category>
      <category>cassandra</category>
      <category>spark</category>
      <category>shell</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2017 19:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1465759</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4333714&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Piyush Rana</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Transformation: An Introduction to DataWeave</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/power-of-transformation-dataweave-introduction?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="2"&gt;When you work with the integration of different systems, sooner or later, you will have to transform data. In today’s world, very few systems talk in the same data language. For example, you may have an HTTP server that&amp;nbsp;understands JSON, but it needs to talk to a server that only understands SOAP XML. Even if it understands JSON, the chances of having same JSON schema or format is very slim, so in these cases, you need to do transform the data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="3"&gt;Mule provides a very powerful tool to do these kinds of transformations: DataWeave.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>integration</category>
      <category>mulesoft</category>
      <category>dataweave</category>
      <category>datasense</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2017 19:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1461394</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4350611&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Hari Kumar</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Target the Application Layer?</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/why-target-the-application-layer?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="2"&gt;When most of us think of applications, we think of the various programs we have downloaded to our smartphones. We interact and make requests of these programs to perform whatever function we need. These requests often, if not always, require the application to communicate with another&amp;nbsp;&lt;img alt="Why Target the Application Layer.png" class="fr-fir fr-dii" sizes="(max-width: 183px) 100vw, 183px" src="https://www.immun.io/hs-fs/hubfs/Blog/Blog_Images/Why%20Target%20the%20Application%20Layer.png?t=1487087529092&amp;amp;width=183&amp;amp;name=Why%20Target%20the%20Application%20Layer.png" srcset="//www.immun.io/hs-fs/hubfs/Blog/Blog_Images/Why%20Target%20the%20Application%20Layer.png?t=1487087529092&amp;amp;width=92&amp;amp;name=Why%20Target%20the%20Application%20Layer.png 92w, //www.immun.io/hs-fs/hubfs/Blog/Blog_Images/Why%20Target%20the%20Application%20Layer.png?t=1487087529092&amp;amp;width=183&amp;amp;name=Why%20Target%20the%20Application%20Layer.png 183w, //www.immun.io/hs-fs/hubfs/Blog/Blog_Images/Why%20Target%20the%20Application%20Layer.png?t=1487087529092&amp;amp;width=275&amp;amp;name=Why%20Target%20the%20Application%20Layer.png 275w, //www.immun.io/hs-fs/hubfs/Blog/Blog_Images/Why%20Target%20the%20Application%20Layer.png?t=1487087529092&amp;amp;width=366&amp;amp;name=Why%20Target%20the%20Application%20Layer.png 366w, //www.immun.io/hs-fs/hubfs/Blog/Blog_Images/Why%20Target%20the%20Application%20Layer.png?t=1487087529092&amp;amp;width=458&amp;amp;name=Why%20Target%20the%20Application%20Layer.png 458w, //www.immun.io/hs-fs/hubfs/Blog/Blog_Images/Why%20Target%20the%20Application%20Layer.png?t=1487087529092&amp;amp;width=549&amp;amp;name=Why%20Target%20the%20Application%20Layer.png 549w" width="183" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;application through an&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://www.immun.io/blog/api-security-an-overview" target="_blank"&gt;API (Application Program Interface)&lt;/a&gt;. For the most part, we don’t think about the protocols needed to make this communication possible, unless something goes wrong. Communication between applications takes place across an IP network, typically using an OSI (Open Systems Interconnection) model, which provides standardized steps that occur at seven distinct layers. The seventh layer, and only layer that users interact with, is the application layer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="3"&gt;For one application to communicate with another application, computer, or data source, the request travels through seven layers of protocols:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>security</category>
      <category>api</category>
      <category>cross-site scripting</category>
      <category>application layer</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2017 18:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1464906</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4350623&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Mike Milner</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Function-as-Object</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/functionasobject?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="2"&gt;In programming, the fundamental notion of an object is the bundling of data and behavior. This provides a common data context when writing a set of related functions. It also provides an interface for manipulating the data that allows the object to control access to that data, making it easy to support derived data and prevent invalid modifications of data. Many languages provide explicit syntax to define classes, which act as definitions for objects. But if you have a language with first-class functions and closures, you can use these constructs to create objects using the 'function-as-object' pattern (originally described by Eugene Wallingford).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="3"&gt;Here is an example of a simplistic person object, done using the function-as-object style in JavaScript.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>javascript</category>
      <category>web dev</category>
      <category>object</category>
      <category>function</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2017 18:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1464563</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4350616&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Martin Fowler</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Technology Landscape in 2017</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/technology-landscape-in-2017?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="1"&gt;As we are still in Q1 of 2017, I decided to write an article about the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://apiumtech.com/blog/top-19-interesting-tech-startups/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;technology landscape&lt;/a&gt; to know what to expect in 2017. We live in a world where everything changes fast, so what I write now may be useless in 1 or 2 years, but at least for the coming months, it may help you to plan your&amp;nbsp;digital&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://apiumtech.com/services/it-consulting-and-training/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;IT strategy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 pid="3"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;M-Commerce is Growing Exponentially&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p pid="5"&gt;Mobile is everything to us now. It helps us keep in touch with family and friends. Stay on top of work, improve fitness, monitor health, manage homes, conduct financial transactions and much, much more. Mobile is changing all industries inside-and-out and giving us huge opportunities. By 2020, &lt;a href="https://apiumtech.com/blog/m-commerce-is-changing-the-fashion-industry-its-time-to-catch-up/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;m-commerce&lt;/a&gt; will represent up to 45 % of total e-commerce, equaling $284 billion in sales. 1 billion people will connect to mobile networks over the next five years, bringing the total number of global mobile subscribers to 5.6 billion, or 72 % of the world’s population, according to the GSMA study. Also, digitization will boost the number of connected devices from 18 billion to 50 billion by 2020 said Chuck Robbins, CEO of Cisco.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>agile</category>
      <category>cloud</category>
      <category>big data</category>
      <category>innovation</category>
      <category>mcommerce</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2017 18:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1463053</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4332507&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Ekaterina Novoseltseva</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Java EE Guardians Survey Results: Java SE 8 Alignment</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/java-ee-guardians-survey-results-java-se-8-alignment?utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_source=feedpress.me&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+dzone</link>
      <description>&lt;p pid="10"&gt;As some of you are aware, the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://javaee-guardians.io/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank" style="background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);"&gt;Java EE Guardians&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and DZone jointly conducted a community survey to help determine Java EE 8 features prior to JavaOne 2016. You may also be aware that&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://java.net/projects/javaee-spec/lists/users/archive/2016-09/message/0" rel="nofollow" target="_blank" style="background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);"&gt;we shared the results of that survey with Oracle&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;before the details of the renewed Java EE 8 scope was announced. Now is a great time to start analyzing those results a bit more. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p pid="10"&gt;I've already done a&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://dzone.com/articles/dzonejava-ee-guardians-survey-results-a-summary" rel="nofollow" style="background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);"&gt;high level summary of the results&lt;/a&gt;. I've also done a deeper dive into the responses for&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://dzone.com/articles/java-ee-guardians-survey-results-http-2servlet-4" rel="nofollow" style="background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);"&gt;HTTP/2 and Servlet 4 support in Java EE 8&lt;/a&gt;. In this entry I'll take a look at the responses for Java SE 8 alignment in Java EE 8.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>java</category>
      <category>java ee</category>
      <category>java se</category>
      <category>java api</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2017 17:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://dzone.com/articles/1464890</guid>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://dzone.com/thumbnail?fid=4335240&amp;w=600"/>
      <dc:creator>Reza Rahman</dc:creator>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
